<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FRAG</title>
    <link>http://fragworks.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on FRAG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 20:26:34 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://fragworks.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding content</title>
      <link>http://fragworks.io/adding-content/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 20:26:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://fragworks.io/adding-content/index/</guid>
      <description>Hello world Let&amp;rsquo;s create our first content file for your documentation. Open a terminal and add the following command for each new file you want to add. Replace &amp;lt;section-name&amp;gt; with a general term that describes your document in detail.
hugo new &amp;lt;section-name&amp;gt;/filename.md  Visitors of your website will find the final document under www.example.com/&amp;lt;section-name&amp;gt;/filename/.
Since it&amp;rsquo;s possible to have multiple content files in the same section I recommend to create at least one index.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadmap</title>
      <link>http://fragworks.io/roadmap/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 20:08:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://fragworks.io/roadmap/index/</guid>
      <description>Quo vadis? The port of the original Alabaster theme has replicated nearly all of its features. A few are still missing, but I&amp;rsquo;ve good news: the Hugo community is actively working on this issues. Maybe with the next release of Hugo we can abandon this list. Stay tuned.
Planned features Localization Currently, it is possible to collect all strings in a single place for easy customization. However, this only enables you to define all strings in a single language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>index</title>
      <link>http://fragworks.io/getting-started/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 00:15:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://fragworks.io/getting-started/index/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FRAG</title>
      <link>http://fragworks.io/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 00:01:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://fragworks.io/index/</guid>
      <description>FRAG - Framework for Rather Awesome Games Introduction FRAG is a cross-platform 2D (eventually 3D) game creation framework for the Nim programming language. It is still very early in its development lifecycle so if you decide to use it, please understand it will be rough around the edges. Please also note that this documentation may be incomplete and or may rapidly change.
 Dependencies Nim Nimble GENie SDL2 SDL_image  Instructions for building and installing the above listed dependencies, are outside of the scope of this document.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>